(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
にころわっ　ころねっ　ころねっ　ころわっ　ころねっ　ころねっ　ころねっ　ころねっ
Ni-koro-wa! Corone! Corone! Coro-wa! Corone! Corone! Corone! Corone!
「いいこと？愚民ども　私のことは
“Listen up, you lowlifes!
ころ様とお呼びなさい」
You shall address me as Koro-sama!”
（あーーー）
(Aaahhh!)
（いーぬっ　いーぬっ　いーぬっ　いーぬっ　いーぬっ　いーぬっ　いーぬっ　いーぬっ）
(Do-og! Do-og! Do-og! Do-og! Do-og! Do-og! Do-og! Do-og!)
「だから　犬じゃなくて　ころ様とお呼びなさいっ」
“I told you, I'm not a dog! Address me as Koro-sama!”
（にころさま　ころさま　ころさま　ころさま　ころさま　ころさま　ころさま　ころさま）
(Ni-Koro-sama! Koro-sama! Koro-sama! Koro-sama! Koro-sama! Koro-sama! Koro-sama! Koro-sama!)
ひれ伏しなさい　人も妖も全て
Bow down before me, humans and youkai alike
ひれ伏しなさい　地べた這いつくばれ
Bow down before me, crawl upon the earth
ひれ伏しなさい　巫女も幽霊も魔女も
Bow down before me, shrine maidens, ghosts, and witches
ひれ伏しなさい　蓬莱の弾幕
Bow down before me, take the Hourai Danmaku
食らえ
right now!
我不死の姫　五つの宝を求め
I am the immortal princess, seeking the five treasures
我不死の姫　千年の満月
I am the immortal princess, the thousand-year full moon
我不死の姫　うつつは幻やぶり
I am the immortal princess, shattering reality and illusions
我不死の姫　蓬莱の樹海に
I am the immortal princess, in the Hourai Sea of Trees
沈んじゃえ
Go sink into it!
（こーねー　こーねー　にーろーねー　こーろねー　こーろねー）
(Ko-ne! Ko-ne! Ni-ro-ne! Koro-ne! Koro-ne!)
（ころねっ　ころねっ　戌神ころねー！）
(Corone! Corone! Inugami Corone!)
（にころねー　こーろー　いぬいぬいぬー）
(Ni-Corone! Koro! Inu inu inu!)
にころわっ　ころねっ　ころねっ　ころわっ　ころねっ　ころねっ　ころねっ　ころねっ
Ni-koro-wa! Corone! Corone! Coro-wa! Corone! Corone! Corone! Corone!
「だーかーらー　ころねじゃなくて　ころ様とお呼びなさいっ」
“I'm telling you! It's not Corone, call me Koro-sama!”
（ゆーびー　ゆーびー　ゆーびー　ゆーびー　ゆーびー　ゆーびー　ゆーびー　ゆーびー）
(Yu-bi! Yu-bi! Yu-bi! Yu-bi! Yu-bi! Yu-bi! Yu-bi! Yu-bi!)
「何よゆびって　この愚民共は言葉もマトモに喋れないのかしらっ」
“What do you mean 'fingers'? Can't you lowlifes even speak properly?”
（おかゆっ　おかゆっ　おかゆっ　おかゆっ　おかゆっ　おかゆっ　おかゆっ　おかゆっ）
(Okayu! Okayu! Okayu! Okayu! Okayu! Okayu! Okayu! Okayu!)
「ちょっと　どうしておかゆになるのよ　そこっ」
“Hey! Why are you chanting 'Okayu' all of a sudden!?”
「もー　仕方ないわねぇ　ちゃんと聞いてなさい　二番いくわよっ　二番」
“Geez, I guess I have no choice. Listen up carefully! We're moving to the second verse!”
永遠の帳　夜を止めて遊べ
Curtain of eternity, stop the night and play
永遠の 姫 今時のゆるさで
Eternal princess, with a modern laxity
永遠の 姫 膝が砕けても踊れ
Eternal princess, dance even if your knees shatter
永遠の 姫 腰が砕けても踊れ
Eternal princess, dance even if your hips shatter
永遠の 姫 倒れることはない たぶん
Eternal princess, you won't fall down, probably
ほらほら ほらほら
Look, look! Look, look!
足舐めなさい これで
Lick my feet, with this...
悦ぶの？ 下僕っ
Are you happy? My servant!
足舐めなさい 肌色透き通る
Lick my feet, my skin is translucent
諦めなさい 所詮
Give up, after all...
卑しき民なのよ
...you are but lowly people
諦めなさい 謎を
Give up on the mystery
あははははははは
Ahahahahahaha
にころねー ころねー ころねー ころねー ころねー！
Ni-Korone! Korone! Korone! Korone! Korone!
にころねー ころねー
Ni-Korone! Korone!
ころねっ ころねっ 戌神ころねー！
Korone! Korone! Inugami Korone!
にころねー ころねー いぇいいぇいおーっ！
Ni-Korone! Korone! Yay, yay, oh!
INUGAMI KORONE'S ANNIVERSARY LIVE 4
はい、ということで、皆様こんばんは！
All right, so, good evening everyone!
はい、えっと、一曲目は「ひれ伏せ愚民どもっ！」ですね
Okay, so, the first song was "Hihifuse Gumindomo!"
歌わせていただきました。ころねすきと一緒にね
I performed it. Together with Koronesuki.
はい、えっと、今日のハッシュタグはですね
Right, today's hashtag is...
戌神ころね4周年 つけて...
..."#InugamiKorone4thAnniversary". Please use it...
よかったらツイートとか画像とかスクショとかいっぱい撮って、
...to tweet, share images or screenshots,
感想ツイートをしてくれると嬉しいなと思います！
and let me know what you think! I'd be very happy!
あれれれ？どうしたの？
Oh? What's wrong?
なんで泣いてるの？
Why are you crying?
えっ、殴られたの？
Eh? Did someone hit you?
誰に？
Who did it?
誰に殴られたの？えっ、どうしたの、どうしたの。おいで、おいで、ほら。
Who hit you? Oh, what happened? Come here, come on.
ころねは優しいよ。ほら、お隣においで、ほら。
Korone is kind. Come on, come stand next to me.
泣かないで、大丈夫だからね。はい、元気になった？
Don't cry, it's okay. There, do you feel better?
あ、よかったよかった。もう、殴る人なんてね、ころねがやっつけてあげるからね。
Ah, good, good. I'll take down anyone who hits you.
わかった？
Understand?
はい、じゃあね、このころねすきが来たということで、いつものやつやる？
Okay then, since Koronesuki is here, shall we do the usual thing?
やろっか。じゃあ...
Let's do it. Now then...
おててを拝借。
Lend me your hands.
もうちょっとこっち来れるかな？
Can you come a bit closer?
あ、おてて見えるかな。行くよ！
Ah, can you see the hands? Here we go!
ゆびゆびー！
Yubi-yubi!
あ！おお！
Ah! Oh!
あ！見て皆様。これが生ゆびゆび...
Ah! Look, everyone. These are fresh fingers...
あ、ちょっと気持ち悪いのであんま映さないほうがいいかもしれない。
Ah, they're a bit gross, so maybe we shouldn't show them too much.
はい、はい、一本じゃ足りない？じゃあ、もう一回。
Yes, yes. One isn't enough? Then one more time.
ゆびゆびー！
Yubi-yubi!
あ！すごいよ！あ。
Ah! Amazing! Oh.
うわ、見てください。とれたての指。
Wow, look at these. Freshly plucked fingers.
これ、大丈夫かな？
Is this okay?
え、二本じゃ足りないの？三本目もいきたいの？
What, two aren't enough? You want a third one too?
いいよ。せーの！
Okay. Ready, go!
ゆびゆびー！
Yubi-yubi!
やばいよ、うわ！
This is crazy, wow!
あ、どっか行っちゃった。見てください皆様。えっと今ね...
Ah, it flew away. Look, everyone. Right now...
ちょっと気持ち悪い... ちょっと気持ち悪いですよちょっとこれ。
It's a bit gross... this is a bit gross.
ちょっと見栄えが悪いので、ちょっとスタッフさんに返して...
It doesn't look very good, so I'll give it back to the staff...
えーと、リスナーさんからね、指を、生指をもらったということで、
So, now that I've received some fresh fingers from the listeners,
次の曲、準備していきたいと思います！
I'll start getting ready for the next song!
ちょっとそのまま待っててね！
Just wait there for a moment!
ちょっと準備してくるね！
I'll go get ready!
ハッピーチルドレン
作詞：新沢としひこ 作曲：中川ひろたか
Happy Children
Lyrics: Shinzawa Toshihiko, Composition: Nakagawa Hirotaka
それは ふしぎな まほうの ちから
That is a mysterious magical power
ぼくと はなすと しあわせに なる
Talking to me will make you happy
だれでも いいさ みみを かしなよ
Anyone's fine, lend me your ear
ほっぺ ゆるんで 笑いたくなる
My cheeks loosen up, and I feel like laughing.
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン おこりんぼは どこ？
Happy children, where is the grumpy one?
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン さみしがりは だれ？
Happy children, who's the lonely one?
それは ふしぎな まほうの ちから
It's a mysterious magical power.
わたしを みると しあわせになる
When you look at me, you'll become happy.
ちょっと みててよ じょうずに スキップ
Watch me for a bit, I skip so well.
きっと いっしょに おどりたくなる
You'll surely want to dance together.
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン いばりんぼは どこ？
Happy children, where is the bossy one?
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン へそまがりは だれ？
Happy children, who's the stubborn one?
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン ぼくらを みてごらん
Happy children, take a look at us.
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン けんかは おしまい
Happy children, fighting is over.
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン ぼくらを みてごらん
Happy children, take a look at us.
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピーチルドレン
Happy, happy, happy children.
ハッピーチルドレン けんかは...
Happy children, fighting...
...おしまい！
...is over!
Danceでバコーン！
作詞・作曲：つんく
Dance de Bakoon!
Lyrics/Composition: Tsunku
沸っキャッシー 旅立つ時間だ
So hyped! It's time to set off.
沸っキャッジョ ときめく時間だ
Feeling great! It's time for my heart to throb.
諦めやしない 私の未来 誰のものでもない
I won't give up; my future belongs to no one else.
もちろんたまの休日 正味も降りたい 毎日が勝負だ
Of course, on a rare holiday, I want to take a break; every day is a battle.
ああ やだ またちょっと太った
Ah, no way. I gained a bit of weight again.
もう やだ 手玉を取らないで
I hate this. Don't toy with me.
ダンスでバコーン！ なんか全部忘れたい
Dance de Bakoon! I want to forget everything somehow.
ダンスでバコーン！ 涙が止まらないよ
Dance de Bakoon! My tears won't stop.
こんなにすごく切ないの
It's so incredibly painful.
どうしてかわかんない
I don't know why.
今まで溜めたストレスを
The stress I've built up until now,
今夜でおさらばさ
I'll say goodbye to tonight.
沸っキャッシ 縁もたけなわだ
So hyped! The party is in full swing.
沸っキャッジョ 主役のこれだ
Feeling great! It's the lead's turn.
輝くしかない うちらの時代 誰にも任せない
We have no choice but to shine; this is our era, and we won't leave it to anyone else.
もちろんバカじゃいけない 時代を呼んで レバレッジ効かせてこう
Of course, we can't be fools; reading the era, let's use some leverage.
ああ やだ また調子に乗ってる
Ah, no way. I'm getting carried away again.
もう やだ 人のせいにしないで
I hate this. Don't blame it on others.
ダンスでバコーン！ 今日は全部忘れるよ
Dance de Bakoon! I'll forget everything today.
ダンスでバコーン！ なぐさめはいらないわ
Dance de Bakoon! I don't need any comfort.
心が随分軽くなる
My heart is becoming much lighter.
お腹が減ってきたわ
I'm getting hungry.
帰りにうどん食べてくわ
I'll go eat some udon on my way home.
明日が待ってるもん
Because tomorrow is waiting.
フー！
Huu!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ダンスでバコーン！
Dance de Bakoon!
今日は全部忘れるよ
Forget everything today
ダンスでバコーン！
Dance de Bakoon!
なぐさめはいらない
I don't need comfort
わん！
Woof!
心がずいぶん軽くなる
My heart feels much lighter
お腹が減ってきたわ
I'm getting hungry
帰りにうどん食べてくわ
I'll eat udon on the way home
明日が待ってるもん！
Because tomorrow is waiting!
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po
太いビート お太鼓
Thick beat, the drum
響かせてオープン
Let it ring out, open
迷い踊れ 浮世（うきよ）
Dance in confusion, the floating world
人の世界を
The world of humans
ジャキジャキ華やいだし
Sparkling and glamorous
ややこしい話に
To complicated stories
蓋をして イェイ 朝まで
Put a lid on it, yeah, until morning
餅つきウサギ 月うさぎ
Mochi-pounding rabbit, moon rabbit
祭り提灯 大明神
Festival lantern, great deity
誰かからもらった飴玉を
The candy I got from someone
舐めずに何度も
I look at it over and over
眺めている
without licking it
賑やか過ぎるの帰り道
The way home is too lively
ほっといてよ
Leave me alone
今だけ一人でニヤけるわ
I'll grin by myself just for now
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po
星にふりまくココロは
The heart scattered to the stars
熱のままにまたたいて
Twinkles while still hot
伝えきれない言の葉
Words that can't be fully conveyed
夜空に咲いた恋花火
Love fireworks blooming in the night sky
イェイ！
Yeah!
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po
傾き（かぶき）もの同士 ノリノリ
Fellow eccentric people, high spirits
刻む流行り拍子
Ticking the trendy beat
見上げた夜空にパッと流れ星
Looking up at the night sky, a shooting star flashes
ひと夜限りの精一杯
My best effort for just one night
わっしょい連打で大盛況
Great success with repeated 'wasshoi' shouts
そのまま夜が更けてくダンダン
The night deepens just like that, step by step
時間も忘れ街外れ
Forgetting time, on the edge of town
だんだん坂の裏通り
The backstreet of Dandan Slope
言えない思いは募るまま
As unspoken feelings continue to grow
さよなら笑顔映している
A goodbye smile is reflected
火照った心の真ん中に
In the middle of a burning heart
振り向いてよ
Please look back
月に独り言つぶやくわ
I'll mutter a monologue to the moon
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po
想うほどに甘くなる
The more I think, the sweeter it gets
真夏の味の飴玉
The midsummer-flavored candy
味わえばすぐ消えてく
Once tasted, it fades away quickly
花火のようにあでやかに
Brilliantly, like fireworks
イェイ！
Yeah!
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po
ゲラゲラポー ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera po, gera gera po
ゲラゲラポッポ ゲラゲラポー
Gera gera poppo, gera gera po
HEY!
Oh!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up, stand up, and stand up!
HEY!
Oh!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up, stand up, and stand up!
イナズマチャレンジャー
Inazuma Challenger
HEY!
ドン底 弱気をパンチング
Down in the dumps, punching through the weakness
トンチを利かせてスライディング
Using my wits, I go sliding
泥んこまみれが
Covered in mud
勇ましく光るぜ！
I'll shine bravely!
貪欲チャレンジ精神
Greedy challenge spirit
Don't cry 逃げずにファイティング
Don't cry, fighting without running away
悔しい気持ちも
Even the frustrating feelings
パワーに変えようぜ
Let's turn them into power
汗かきべそかき夢育ち
Sweating, crying, growing with dreams
根っ子はマグマ稲妻魂
The roots are magma lightning soul
傷だらけの勲章ジャングル
The jungle of battle-scarred medals
見た目オンボロ中身骨太
Worn out on the outside, sturdy on the inside
HEY!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
ピンチの谷から日の出
The sunrise from the valley of pinches
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
イナズマファイター
Lightning Fighter
HEY!
ドンマイ負けるなスタンディング
Don't mind, don't lose, keep standing
行くぜ世界へジャンピング
Let's go, jumping to the world
弱気になるなよ
Don't get discouraged
立ち向かえ青春
Face your youth head-on
ど根性バリキのエンジン
Gutsy horsepower engine
Don't Stop くじけず前進
Don't Stop, advance without faltering
相手が強けりゃ
If the opponent is strong
強いほど燃えるぜ
I'll burn all the more
向かい風のようなシュート
A shot like a headwind
四方八方から攻めて来ても
Even if they attack from all sides
最後の大砦抜かせねーぞ
I won't let them through the final stronghold
あの娘にいいトコ見せてやれ皆の衆
Show that girl your best side, everyone
HEY!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
曇天蹴飛ばし日本晴れ
Kicking away the cloudy skies, a clear Japanese day
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
イナズマチャレンジャー
Lightning Challenger
HEY!
リーヨ！
Riyo!
この日々の努力も
These daily efforts too
あの日々の悔しさも
And the frustrations of those days
全部 全部 全部 全部 全部
All, all, all, all, all of it
燃えろ 燃えろ 燃えろ 皆の衆！
Burn, burn, burn, everyone!
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
ねじりはちまき気合１００倍
With a twisted headband, 100 times the spirit
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
勇気のシンボルイナズママーク
Symbol of courage, the lightning mark
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
掲げよう勝利のフラッグを
Let's hoist the flag of victory
Stand up Stand up 立ち上がリーヨ
Stand up Stand up Stand up-riyo
イナズマファイター
Lightning Fighter
イナズマ
Lightning
（ファイト！）
(Fight!)
イナズマヒーロー
Lightning Hero
HEY!
Oh!
でびちゃーん！
Debi-chan!
いぬころー、来てやったぞー。
Inukoro, I'm here.
ありがと、でびちゃん。
Thank you, Debi-chan.
うれしー！
I'm so happy!
よっこらしょ。
Heave-ho.
今日さ、めでたいらしいね。
I heard today's a special occasion.
そう、今日ね、ころね4周年迎えたんだよ。
Yeah, today's Korone's 4th anniversary.
ほー。
Oh.
あのね、でびちゃんとね、記念ライブでね、歌って踊りたかったから、今日はすごい夢叶っちゃったよ。
I really wanted to sing and dance with Debi-chan in a commemorative live, so my dream came true today.
んー、よかったねー。
Hmm, that's good.
ま、たまにはこういうのもいいもんじゃね。また遊んでやってもいいぞ。
Well, something like this every now and then isn't bad. I'm willing to play with you again.
え、本当に？
Wait, really?
じゃあ、またゲームとか一緒にやろう。
Then let's play games together again.
ま、いいよー。
Well, fine.
じゃあ、このあとも頑張りたまえ。ではな。
Well, keep up the good work for the rest of this. See ya.
ありがとでびちゃん、またね、気をつけてね。
Thank you Debi-chan, see you, take care.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
帰っていきました、デビちゃんが。
Debi-chan is heading back.
デビちゃん、ありがとう！
Debi-chan, thank you!
ね、ちょっと次もゲストを呼んでるんですが、
Well, I'm calling the next guest now,
ちょっと個人的にすごい緊張してて、
but I'm personally very nervous,
あの、ものすごい人を呼んでいまして。
because I've called someone incredible.
ちょっと緊張するんで一回どきます。
I'm so nervous, I'll step aside for a moment.
緊張します。どうしよう。
I'm nervous. What should I do?
夜空の星が輝く陰で
Behind the stars of the night sky,
悪の笑いがこだまする
The laughter of evil echoes
星から星になく人の涙背負って宇宙の始末
Carrying the tears of those who cry from star to star, cleaning up the universe
銀河旋風ブライガー
Ginga Senpuu Braiger
お呼びとあらば即参上！
Called upon, we arrive!
銀河旋風ブライガー
作詞・作曲 山本正之
Ginga Senpuu Braiger
Lyrics/Music: Masayuki Yamamoto
J9 J9 情無用
J9, J9, no mercy
アステロイド・ベルトの
In the asteroid belt,
アウトローも震えだす
Even the outlaws start to tremble
コズモレンジャーJ9
Cosmo Ranger J9!
宇宙空間つっぱしるのさ
Dashing through outer space,
ブライサンダー ブライサンダー
Brai-Thunder, Brai-Thunder
十万光年星のきらめき
The sparkle of stars 100,000 light-years away
飛び交うブライスター
Flying around, Brai-Star
拡がるプラズマ ウ・ウ・ウルフのマーク
Expanding plasma, the mark of the w-w-wolf
ア・ア・アイツは
T-t-that guy is...
銀河旋風
Ginga Senpuu...
ブライガー
Braiger!
J9 J9 恐れ無用
J9, J9, no fear
悪の限り暴れろ
Go wild with all the evil you have
アウトローも逃げてゆく
Even the outlaws run away
コズモレンジャーJ9
Cosmo Ranger J9!
スーパーポリス自慢のマシン
Super Police's pride and joy machine,
ブライサンダー ブライサンダー
Brai-Thunder, Brai-Thunder
命知らずを乗せてはるかに
Carrying the daredevils far away,
飛び立つブライスター
Taking off, Brai-Star
拡がるプラズマ ウ・ウ・ウルフのマーク
Expanding plasma, the mark of the w-w-wolf
ア・ア・アイツは
T-t-that guy is...
銀河旋風
Ginga Senpuu...
ブライガー
Braiger!
ブライガー！ブライガー！
Braiger! Braiger!
ブライガー！
Braiger!
ということでなんとたいらいさおさんがいらしてくださいました！
So, to my surprise, Isao Taira-san has come!
はい、たいらいさおでございます。
Yes, I am Isao Taira.
ころねさん、4周年おめでとうございます！
Korone-san, congratulations on your 4th anniversary!
あー！ありがとうございます！
Ah! Thank you so much!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
こちらも嬉しいです。
I'm happy too.
いやもう、今ちょっと緊張と嬉しさでいろいろ感情が大変なことになっておりまして。
I'm just so nervous and happy right now, my emotions are all over the place.
あらあら。
Oh my.
絶対みんなも聞いたことある、名曲アニソンの数々を歌ってらっしゃるすごい方なんです。
He's an incredible person who has sung many famous anime songs that everyone must have heard.
ありがとうございます、丁寧なご紹介を。
Thank you for such a polite introduction.
まさかの、前回の3Dライブでころねが歌った『復活のイデオン』を、なんとたいらいさおさんが聞いてくださって。
Surprisingly, Taira Isao-san actually listened to my performance of 'Fukkatsu no Ideon' from my previous 3D live.
くださってるじゃない、聞いたんですよもう、びっくり。
I didn't just 'listen', I heard it! I was so surprised.
とっても可愛い声のイデオンが聞こえてきて、とっても嬉しかったです。
Hearing an Ideon with such a cute voice made me very happy.
ありがとうございます。今回ね、ころねが「たいらいさおさん、よかったらライブに出てくれませんか」とお声をかけてみたらですね。
Thank you. This time, I asked, "Taira Isao-san, if you'd like, would you appear in my live?"
なんとなんと快く「いいですよ」とお受けしてくださりましてですね。
And he very graciously agreed, saying, "That would be fine."
そんな丁寧に言わないでいいですよ。本当にありがとうございます。
You don't have to be so polite. Thank you so much.
こちらこそありがとうございます。
Thank you as well.
こんなね、僕のこの大切な一曲をころねさんとジョイントできるなんて、
To be able to do a joint performance of this precious song of mine with Korone-san...
こんな最高なことないじゃないですか。もう喜んできましたよ。
There's nothing better than this. I came here with joy.
ありがとうございます。今回はね、来ていただいただけでなく、名曲『銀河旋風ブライガー』を一緒に歌っていただいて。
Thank you. This time, not only did you come here, but you also sang the masterpiece 'Ginga Senpuu Braiger' with me.
あの、振りまで一緒に、J9, J9ってね、Jという形なんですけど。
And we even did the choreography together, the 'J9, J9' part, which is in the shape of a 'J'.
これでいつも動きやってる、J9, J9ってやってくれて、ありがとう。
I always do that movement, so thank you for doing 'J9, J9' with me.
歌い方も教えていただいて、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for teaching me how to sing it.
いえいえ、何にも教えてないですよ、もうころね節で十分です。
No, no, I didn't teach you anything. Your 'Korone-style' was more than enough.
たいらいさおさんはバーチャル空間初めてだと思うんですけど、どうですか、来てみて？
I think this is Taira Isao-san's first time in a virtual space, but how is it being here?
初めてですね。
It is my first time.
どんな感じしました？
How did it feel?
変な感じではないよ。
It didn't feel strange.
あ、馴染んでますもんね。
Ah, you're blending in well.
もうなんか楽しくころねさんと歌えてるなっていう気持ちだけで、
I just feel like I'm having fun singing with Korone-san...
もう馴染んでます。大丈夫。
...so I'm already adjusted. It's fine.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
あ、ちなみに、もう一曲一緒に歌ってもらうことって可能でしょうか？
By the way, would it be possible to have you sing one more song together?
もちろんですよ。
Of course.
本当ですか！ありがとうございます！
Really? Thank you!
こちらこそよろしくお願いします。
The pleasure is mine.
ありがとうございます。えっと、ころねの大好きなこの曲を、ではお願いしたいと思います。
Thank you. Well then, I'd like to ask you to perform this song that I love.
僕もこの曲でころねさんのことをよく知りましたので。
I also got to know Korone-san well through this song.
じゃあもう、みんなも何が来るか分かってると思うけど、タイトル一緒にお願いしてもいいでしょうか。
Then, I think everyone already knows what's coming, but could we say the title together?
はい、いいですよ。
Yes, sure.
いきます！せーの！
Here we go! Ready, set...
復活のイデオン！
Resurrection of Ideon!
復活のイデオン
Resurrection of Ideon
きこえるか きこえるだろう はるかな 轟き
Can you hear it? You must hear it, the distant roar.
闇の中 魂ゆさぶる 目覚め始まる
In the darkness, a soul-shaking awakening begins.
大地わり そそり立つ姿 正義の証か
Cleaving the earth, its towering form... Is it a symbol of justice?
伝説の巨神の力 銀河きりさく
The power of the legendary giant god slices through the galaxy.
おたけびが 電光石火の一撃をよぶ
The battle cry calls forth a lightning-fast strike.
ふるえるな 瞳こらせよ 復活の時
Do not tremble, fix your gaze, it is the time of resurrection.
人よ 生命よ 始まりを見る
Oh people, oh life, witness the beginning.
スペース・ランナウェイ イデオン イデオン
Space runaway Ideon, Ideon.
たたかうか たたかえるか おびえる魂よ
Will you fight? Can you fight? Oh, trembling soul.
せまりくる 悪の力に 勇気を示せ
Show your courage against the approaching forces of evil.
宇宙にとぶ 輝く姿 生命の叫びか
Flying into space, its shining form... Is it the cry of life?
伝説の巨神の力 銀河きりさく
The power of the legendary giant god slices through the galaxy.
必殺の 技が撃つのは 我が身なのかと
Is it myself that the ultimate technique strikes?
おそれるな 魂ひらけよ 復活の時
Do not fear, open your soul, it is the time of resurrection.
人よ 生命よ 力をみる
Oh people, oh life, witness the power.
スペース・ランナウェイ イデオン イデオン
Space runaway Ideon, Ideon.
やったね！
We did it!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
あの、この曲は前回も歌ったんですけど、歌った理由としては本当に大好きな曲で。
Um, I sang this song last time too, but the reason I sang it is that I really love it.
嬉しいね。
That's good to hear.
入りから、優しくたいらさんの歌声が聞こえてきたと思ったら、
From the beginning, I heard Taira-san's gentle voice,
力強くどんどんなっていって、歌が。
and then it got stronger and stronger, the song.
それが凄い聞いてて凄い気持ちよくて、大好き。
Listening to that felt so good, I love it.
そうそうそこがこの歌の、イデオンの良い所ですよ。
Exactly, that's the good thing about this song, Ideon.
あの静かな立ち上がりでね、そっからロックになっていくというね。
That quiet start, and from there it turns into rock.
そう、本当に格好良い曲で。
Yes, it's a truly cool song.
特にね、ころねさん、2番の歌詞のね、今日ころねさん歌ってくれた
Especially, Korone-san, the lyrics of the second verse that you sang today,
「たたかうか、たたかえるか、おびえる心よ」なんて、もうグッときますよね。
'Will you fight? Can you fight? Oh, trembling heart,' it really hits home.
グッときました。
It really hit home.
今日も隣で、本当に一緒に歌っていただいて、本当に2曲ともありがとうございました。
Singing together with you by my side today as well, thank you so much for both songs.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
じゃあ、そろそろあれですかね、お別れの時間なんでしょうか。
Well, is it about time... time to say goodbye?
あ、そう。そうなの？
Oh, is that so?
そうなんでしょうかね。
I wonder.
じゃあ、ゆびゆびかな？
Then, 'yubi yubi' maybe?
ゆびゆびで、じゃあ最後はお別れで。
With 'yubi yubi,' let's say our final goodbyes.
本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you so much.
こちらこそありがとうございました。ありがとうございました。
Thank you as well. Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました。ゆびゆび。
Thank you. Yubi yubi.
またよろしくね。
See you again.
じゃあ、ころねも準備があるから、ちょっと行ってくるね。
Then, I have some preparations to do, so I'll be going now.
はい、これからも頑張ってください。
Yes, keep doing your best.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
夕暮れの かなたから 蜃気楼
A mirage from beyond the twilight
会いたくて 会いたくて 会えなくて 会えなくて
Wanting to see you, wanting to see you, but unable to meet
あなた ユートピア
You are my utopia
いつの日か この場所で 出会えるなら
If we can meet here again someday
I MISS YOU, I MISS YOU, I NEED YOU, I NEED YOU
Sexy Sexy
ねえ？ 部屋にこない？
Hey, won't you come to my room?
ナイショの話
A secret conversation
聞かせてあげる
I'll let you hear it
今宵 ノレないなら
If you're not feeling it tonight
TAKE AWAY しても
Even if you take me away
どうしようもないね
There's nothing that can be done
ふらちな夜に心も濡れた
My heart was also drenched in this scandalous night
時はもどせない
Time cannot be turned back
COME BACK, COME BACK, COME BACK
情熱の かなたから 蜃気楼
A mirage from beyond the passion
揺らして 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying
気持ちいいこと パラダイス
Feeling good things, paradise
燃えさかる あの場所で 出会えるなら
If we can meet in that place that's burning bright
揺らして 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying
Sexy Sexy Dance
星は青ざめ 花は乱れる
The stars turn pale, the flowers are in disarray
ヤミのなかから キラキラと 映してるの
They're reflecting glitteringly from within the darkness
からみつく 指先の 蜃気楼
A mirage on my intertwining fingertips
じらして じらして じらして じらして
Teasing, teasing, teasing, teasing
ジリジリ いかせて
Tease me bit by bit
いつまでも このあたりで 恋してる
I'll be in love around here forever
I MISS YOU, I MISS YOU, I NEED YOU, I NEED YOU
Sexy Sexy You
OH BABY, MY BABY, AH BABY, OH BABY
あなた ユートピア
You are my utopia
情熱の かなたには 蜃気楼
In the distance of passion, there's a mirage
揺らして 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying
何度も 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして 揺らして
Swaying many times, swaying, swaying, swaying
キラキラと Sexy Sexy
Glittering and Sexy Sexy
Are my eyes deceiving me?
Your soul starts to fade
Unleash your magic to me
Now it's time not to worry
Do believe in me
A journey we have to see
Rurira rarira ira rarira Incomplete melody
Sung with a sweet but yet a sad symphony
Unwavering spirit that you told me.
How can I do it when you're not even here
Oh, let me
Let out the words I could say to you right now
I can only tell you a BIT
Overwhelm me with your kindness is a GIFT
that I could never ever trade
...that I could never ever trade with anything.
Let the time send this song to your ears.
I hope one day you will sing it to me.
Versatile melody that I tried to write.
Every day I would pray in my heart,
cause I'm reaching the sky.
In a time full of worries,
no light I could see.
Do you want me to be here?
Nulling all the emotions
you're supposed to feel.
Even voice I wanna hear.
Shalala Shalila, Incomplete melody.
Arriving in your ears like it's destiny.
Rurira rarira, Incomplete memory.
Showing all the warmth that I have ever feel.
呼んで
Call me
Sing out, 夜の記憶
Sing out, memories of the night
Shout out, 火は燃える
Shout out, fire is burning
星屑の欠片たちは
The fragments of stardust
今 世界になる
are becoming the world now.
新たな喜びを願うの
Wishing for a new joy.
Rurira rarira, a complete melody.
Has been sung in the world so far you can't see.
Let the wind, let the sea carry this melody.
Legacy, timeless song that carry all the wish.
I believe.
All the words I could say right now, I can only tell you a little bit.
Overwhelm me with your kindness a bit.
that I could never ever trade with anything.
Let the time send this song to you.
I hope one day you will sing it to me.
Versatile melody that I tried to write.
Every day I will sing it aloud,
and I will try to shine.
この声を聴いて
Listen to this voice
Terima kasih untuk semua perhatian yang telah kuterima
Thank you for all the support I've received.
As gentle breeze passed through your soul this time.
I believe everything will be fine.
Every day I would sing it aloud,
this is my time to shine.
はい、ということで、えーと、マリンとリスちゃんと、歌った歌を2曲続けて聴いてもらいました！
Alright, so, I just sang two songs in a row with Marine and Risu!
どうだったみんなー！
How was it, everyone?!
マリンとはね、あの『Sexy Sexy』っていう歌をね、ころねが大好きな歌なんだけど、マリンと合うかな？と思って歌って、
With Marine, we sang 'Sexy Sexy.' It's a song I love, and I thought it would suit her perfectly,
リスちゃんのオリ曲をね、ずっと歌いたかったの。
and I've always wanted to sing Risu's original song.
だから今回ちょっとね、たぶん発音めちゃめちゃだったと思うけど、頑張って覚えて、
So this time, though my pronunciation was probably all over the place, I worked hard to learn it
一緒に歌いたいなと思って今回歌えて、すごい嬉しかった。二人ともありがとー！
because I really wanted to sing it with her. I'm so happy I could do it. Thank you both!
あー楽しかったねー。楽しかったと言ってもね、まだ続くんですけどね。
Man, that was fun. Though I say that, there's still more to come.
ころさーん！
Koro-san!
何？ 怖い。
What? That's scary.
ころさーん！
Koro-san!
何？ 怖い。
What? That's scary.
どっしゃあ！ おかゆっすー！
Tada! It's Okayu!
ころさん4周年おめでとう！
Koro-san, happy 4th anniversary!
ありがとう、おかゆ！
Thank you, Okayu!
おかゆもさ、あの今月の6日だっけ？ 6日に4周年だったから、
Okayu also had her 4th anniversary on the 6th of this month, right?
二人でね、迎えましたー！
So we both celebrated together!
そう、二人で迎えました。
Yeah, we did.
見えてる！
I can see you!
おかころだよ！ おかころ！
It's OkaKoro! OkaKoro!
おかころでおかころといえば、いつもね、狂ったMCが定番なんですけど。
Speaking of OkaKoro, crazy MC segments are our standard, but...
確かに。狂ったMC…そうだね。今回もじゃあ何か…
True. Crazy MCs... Right. Shall we do something this time too?
何か思い出ある？おかころでさ、やったことでさ。
Do you have any memories? Of things we've done as OkaKoro.
やっぱね、二人でバイクに乗ってるコントみたいなやつが、やっぱ思い出深いかな。
I'd say that skit where we're both riding a motorcycle is pretty memorable.
やっとく？知らない人もいるから、「何バイク？」って。
Should we do it? There might be people who don't know it and are like, "What motorcycle?"
そうだ、今大人数の人が見てくれてるから、初めて見るよって人も多分いるから。
Right, since so many people are watching now, there are probably some seeing it for the first time.
え、ちょっと待って、迎えに来るわ。
Wait, I'll go pick you up.
わかった。じゃあ、ここら辺で…
Got it. I'll wait around here...
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
ころさん、まだかなー？
I wonder if Koro-san is here yet?
（バイクの音マネ）
(Mimicking motorcycle sounds)
あ、つかない、つかないエンジンが。あれ？
Ah, it won't start, the engine won't start. Huh?
なんか、エンストしてる？
Is it stalling?
（エンジンの音）ブンブンブブブン！
(Engine sounds) Vroom vroom vroom!
きたきたきた！
Here she comes!
待って、乗ってないから！追いかけて！
Wait, I'm not on yet! Chase after her!
あ、おかゆ迎えに来たよ。
Ah, I came to pick you up, Okayu.
あ、ありがと、ありがと。よいしょ。
Ah, thanks, thanks. Ups-a-daisy.
いくよ？つかまってな？
Ready? Hold on tight.
いい？腰につかまってるんだよ。オッケー。
Okay? Hold onto my waist. Got it.
ブンブンブブブン！
Vroom vroom vroom!
なんで、おかゆの方が速いの？あれ？なんか自転車みたいになってる。
Why is Okayu faster? Huh? It's like a bicycle now.
みんなで漕ぐやつ、3人、4人くらいで。あれになってるから。
Like those multi-person cycles, for 3 or 4 people. That's what it turned into.
公園とかにあるやつね。そうそう。
The kind you see in parks. Exactly.
え、待って、ころさんのさ、なんか可愛いのあれ！
Wait, Koro-san, what's that cute thing over there!
あのさ、ここ、そう、ステージ作ったんだよ。凄くない？
You know, this... yeah, I had this stage made. Isn't it amazing?
凄い、可愛い！
Wow, so cute!
え、ちょっと気になるところさ、おかゆ、どこか気になるところある？
Is there any part that catches your eye, Okayu?
え、それ？これ気になるよ！
Eh, that? This part really interests me!
え、これ、じゃあ、カメラさん映してもらっていい？これ。
Oh, this? Camera-san, could you show this, please?
あ、これ。写真撮ろうよ。あ、いいよ。はい、せーの、ピース！
Ah, this. Let's take a photo. Sure. Ready, set, peace!
え、なんで一人なの！一緒に撮ろうよ！
Wait, why just you! Let's take it together!
はい。じゃあ、ピース、せーの、ピース！
Okay. Peace then. Ready, set, peace!
わあ。そう、ステージを今回ね、新しく運営さんに作ってもらって。
Wow. Yeah, the staff made a brand new stage for me this time.
なんかちょっとゲームっぽいような。ゲームが好きだから、ちょっとこんな感じに。
It's kind of game-like. Since I love games, I asked for this style.
で、細い犬とか太い犬も後ろにいて。凄い！
And there's Thin Dog and Fat Dog in the back too. Amazing!
あ、ごめん。おかゆが作ってくれたベロ犬はいないんだけど。
Ah, sorry. Tongue-out Dog that you made for me isn't here though.
なんでベロ犬いないの！
Why isn't Tongue-out Dog here!
違う、ちょっとあの…二軍だね、あの子は。なんで！ごめん！
No, it's just... he's in the reserve team. Why! Sorry!
違うの、次、次機会があったら作るから！本当？
Wait, I'll include him next time if there's a chance! Really?
心の中にはいるよ、ベロ犬が。心の中に…
Tongue-out Dog is in our hearts. In our hearts...
ちょっと嫌じゃない？なんでよ。
Isn't that a bit creepy? Why?
ベロベロ…確かに嫌かも。じゃあ、捨てとくわ。なんでや！
Slurp slurp... True, might be annoying. I'll toss him then. Hey!
はい！えー。
Okay! Geez.
じゃあ、おかゆがベロ犬になってくれたらいいかな。ベロ猫っていうことで。ベロベロ〜！
Well, maybe Okayu could be the Tongue-out Dog. Or Tongue-out Cat. *Slurp slurp!*
あー、ちょっと嬉しい！ということで、はい。
Ah, that actually makes me happy! Anyway, right.
え、こんなんでいいのかな？いいんじゃない？
Is this okay? It's fine, isn't it?
いい？え、もう、なんかやりたいことある？
Is it? So, is there anything else you want to do?
いや、ころさん忘れてるじゃん。
Wait, Koro-san, you've forgotten.
今日は二人で歌歌おうって話だったじゃん。あ、確かに！
We talked about singing a song together today. Oh, right!
そうだよ。
That's right.
歌歌おうよ。確かに歌おう、歌おう！
Let's sing. Yes, let's sing, let's sing!
歌歌おうって。なんか全部飛んじゃった。
Singing a song. It all just slipped my mind.
じゃあ、歌お。あのさ、おかゆとさ、今回なんか…
Let's sing then. You see, this time with Okayu...
おかゆ誘いたくって、歌いたい曲があったんよ。
I really wanted to invite you because there was a song I wanted to sing.
だから、今回その歌をね、おかゆと一緒に歌ってくれないかなーって言って。
So I asked if you'd sing that song with me this time.
でおかゆはね、「え、いいよ、ころさんのためなら僕はどこにでも行くよ」みたいなこと言ってくれて。
And Okayu was like, "Sure, I'll go anywhere for you, Koro-san."
ちょっと盛ってるね。ちょっと盛ったけど。
You're exaggerating a bit. A little bit, yeah.
今回はね、でもおかゆは「いいよ」って言ってくれて。今回この曲を一緒に歌いたいと思います！
But you did say "Sure". So, we're going to sing this song together!
はい。オッケーです。
Yes. Got it.
いいですか？オッケーです。みんな、じゃあここスクショして。可愛いから。
Ready? Ready. Everyone, take a screenshot here. It's cute.
どんぐり。どんぐり。
Donguri. Donguri.
松ぼっくり。松ぼっくり。イエーイ！
Matsubokkuri. Matsubokkuri. Yay!
よし。じゃあ歌いますか。歌いましょう！
Alright. Shall we sing? Let's do it!
ということで、では聴いてください。
And so, please listen.
せーの、カラフル！ちょっとあれだね、ずれたけど、カラフル。
Ready, set, Colorful! We were a bit out of sync, but Colorful.
カラフル
作詞・作曲：渡辺翔
Colorful
Lyrics & Composition: Sho Watanabe
ずっとモノクロだった瞳の奥の
Deep in my eyes that had always been monochrome
景色捨てたら 夢見つけた
Once I cast away that scenery, I found a dream
何もない世界で作る絆は
The bonds we forge in a world with nothing
強い意志与えた
Gave me a strong will
ほら裏返した日常でまた
Look, in our flipped-upside-down everyday life
走って行く先に君はいた
You were there at the end of the road I ran
触れた心は輝いて 鮮やかな色になって
The heart I touched shines and turns into vivid colors
羽ばたくよ 希望乗せて
I'll spread my wings, carrying hope
無限に広がる空の
Under the infinitely
下集まった
expanding sky we gathered
願い守り進めば
If we move forward protecting our wishes
まだ誰も知らない
Toward a tomorrow that
明日へと
no one knows yet
引き寄せられるように
As if being drawn in
覗いた瞬間
the moment I took a peek
光の糸は
Threads of light
秘密包んで
enveloped the secret
細く千切れそうな
Thin and seemingly about to snap
絡まった運命
an entangled fate
一歩また
With another step
変われる
I can change
間違えても信じた道は
Even if I make mistakes, the path I believed in
新しい景色を
will surely illuminate
照らすだろう
a new landscape
巡る時の中で笑って
Laughing amidst the cycling of time
様々な思い持って
carrying various feelings
始めよう また一から
Let's start, once again from the beginning
辿り着いた儚い奇跡
The fleeting miracle we reached
壊れないように
so that it doesn't break
手を伸ばし
reach out your hand
繋げば
and if we connect
ほら君は側で
Look, you are by my side
いつまでも…
forever...
まだ透明な
We who are
私たちは
still transparent
どんな色にでも
because we can be dyed
染まることが出来るから
in any color at all
夢叶えよう
let's make our dreams come true
走って行く先に君はいた
You were there at the end of the run
触れた
Touched
心は輝いた
my heart shone
鮮やかな色になって
becoming a vivid color
羽ばたくよう
Carrying these thoughts
想いを乗せて
as if to take flight
無限に広がる空の
Under the infinitely
下集まった
expanding sky we gathered
願い守り行けば
If we go protecting our wishes
君と誓ったあの日の記憶
The memories of that day I promised you
今越えて過去から
Now crossing over from the past
まだ誰も知らない
Toward a tomorrow that
明日へと
no one knows yet
はぁ〜！カラフルエモかったよねー！
Haa~! "Colorful" was so emotional, wasn't it?
おかゆありがとう！
Okayu, thank you!
はい、ではでは、毎年恒例のこちら出ました！
All right, then, it's that time of year again!
はーい！ころねちゃーん！こんばんわにゃん！
Hello! Korone-chan! Good evening, nyan!
猫妖怪、ジバニャンにゃん！
It's the cat yo-kai, Jibanyan nyan!
ころねちゃんが4周年ライブをやるって聞いて、駆けつけてきたにゃんよ！
I heard Korone-chan was doing a 4th anniversary live, so I rushed over here, nyan!
デビュー4周年、本当におめでとにゃん！
Happy 4th anniversary since your debut, nyan!
ライブめちゃくちゃ盛り上がってるにゃんね！
The live is really heating up, nyan!
オレっちもついつい踊り出したくなっちゃうにゃん。
Even I feel like dancing, nyan.
そういえば、オレっちの目覚まし時計を使ってくれてたりくれてなかったりって聞いたにゃん。
By the way, I heard you might be using my alarm clock, nyan.
ありがとにゃんね！
Thank you, nyan!
ちゃんと起きられてたにゃんか？
Were you able to wake up properly, nyan?
とっても長い時間配信やってるみたいだから、ちゃんと眠れてるか心配にゃん。
Since it seems you stream for a very long time, I'm worried if you're sleeping properly, nyan.
たまにはチョコボー食べてゴロゴロするといいにゃん。
You should eat a Chocobar and relax every once in a while, nyan.
じゃ、ころねちゃん、これからも頑張ってくれにゃん！
Well, Korone-chan, keep doing your best from now on, nyan!
オレっちも応援してるにゃん！
I'm cheering for you, too, nyan!
バイバイにゃん！
Bye-bye nyan!
ユビユビニャン！
Yubi yubi nyan!
え、ちょっと待って... え、待って。本当に知らなかったんだけど。
Wait, hold on... Wait. I really didn't know about this.
え？え？待って、ジバニャン... えー！
What? What? Wait, Jibanyan... Aaah!
ジバニャンありがとう！目覚まし時計はちょっと壊れちゃったんだけど...
Jibanyan, thank you! The alarm clock is actually a bit broken, but...
嬉しい...
I'm so happy...
あの、え、ジバニャンの目覚まし時計を使っててですね、あの、使いすぎて壊れまして...
Well, I was using Jibanyan's alarm clock, but I used it so much it broke...
えーっと...あの、早く、早く、早く、みたいになったんですけど、それがね...
Um... I was like, "hurry, hurry, hurry," but then...
えっ、あ、すごい！なんか、えっ、ジバニャン！ありがとね、ジバニャン！
Eh? Ah, amazing! Like, eh, Jibanyan! Thank you, Jibanyan!
えっ待ってグッズ、グッズ出すテンションでいたのに...
Wait, I was in the mood to show the merchandise...
あの、え、どうしよう、え、これグッズ、あ、紹介...えっ、ジバニャンありがとね、嬉しい！
Um, eh, what should I do? These goods, ah, introducing... Eh, Jibanyan, thank you! I'm so happy!
ということであの、グッズも出ます！すいません、どーんと！
So, the merchandise will also be released! Sorry, boom!
やだーこんなテンションで。はい、戌神ころね活動4周年記念グッズ出まーす！
Oh my, I'm so hyped. Yes, Inugami Korone's 4th Anniversary Merchandise is coming out!
紹介したほうがいいんですよね。はい、あ、こちらですね。えーっとまず初めに、
I should introduce them, right? Yes, ah, here they are. Um, first of all...
「ラバーマット」。こちらは、え、ひこさん先生描き下ろしのデザインとなっておりまして、
The Rubber Mat. This features a design drawn by Hikosun-sensei,
こののどかなね、村をケダマコーネを散歩させてるコーネみたいな感じのラバーマットになっておりますので、
and it's a rubber mat showing Korone taking Kedama-kone for a walk in this peaceful village.
あの、すごい、あの、ほんわかした気持ちになれると思います。可愛い、これめちゃ可愛い。で、次、
I think it'll make you feel very heartwarming. It's cute, this is so cute. Next...
「ケダマコーネぬいぐるみ」。これマジめっちゃ可愛いからね。これはね、あのお洋服も脱げるようになってて、
The Kedama-kone Plushie. This is really, really cute. You can even take off its clothes.
「なんで脱げるようになってんねん」って話でしょ。え、また第2弾が出るんですか？みたいな、それはわかんないけどね。
You're probably thinking, "Why can you take them off?" Like, is there a second series coming? I don't know about that, though.
でもこれ脱げるようになってるんで、なんか着せ替えとかもね、これからできるだーってしたいなーみたいな感じのぬいぐるみとなっております。
But since they're removable, I hope you can enjoy dressing it up in the future. That's the kind of plushie it is.
はい、で、次。「ケダマコーネのジャージ」。これは、ケダマコーネなんだけど、これはねコーネが描きました。
Yes, next. The Kedama-kone Jersey. This is Kedama-kone, and Korone designed this herself.
骨のデザイン、なんかあの男の子も女の子も、老若男女問わず、
The bone design... I made it so that regardless of age or gender, anyone can wear it...
こうなんかかっこよく着こなせるようなかっこいいデザインにしてみました。
...and look cool in it. I tried to create a really stylish design.
であの、胸元にね、あのバックロージャーっぽいようなハート型も書いてあって、
And on the chest, I drew a heart shape that looks a bit like a back-closure.
え、ちょっとすごいねコーネちょっと結構頑張ってデザインしたのでこれよかったらねあの皆さんに着てほしいなーと思います。
I worked quite hard on the design, so I'd love for everyone to wear it.
あとサイズはXLで統一になっちゃうんですけどよかったら是非是非、あの着てね。
Also, the size is only available in XL, but please wear it if you like.
はい、で、フルセット。こちらフルセット買っていただいた方には、コーネが描き下ろしたこのね、あのステッカーなんですけど、
Yes, and the Full Set. For those who buy the Full Set, there's this sticker set that Korone drew.
あの名前がね、こうピプピプピプって書けるようになってるんで、これね、あの新学期始まったらね、これをノートとかね、
You can write your names on them. If you put these on your notebooks or bags...
カバンとかに貼ってたら「何それ！？」みたいな、人気者になれること間違いなしなので、是非是非、あの買ってください。
...when the new school year starts, you'll definitely become popular! So please, please buy them.
はい。ということで、ケダマコーネっていうのはね、あの砂漠先生っていう方が生み出してくださったんですけど、本当に砂漠先生ありがとうございました。
So, Kedama-kone was created by Sabaku-sensei. Thank you so much, Sabaku-sensei.
はい。今回はね、あのケダマコーネのね、あのいっぱいグッズを作ったので、ぜひあの見てみてね。あのこの後10時から発売です。よろしくね。
I've made lots of Kedama-kone merchandise this time, so please check them out. They go on sale from 10 PM! Thank you.
はい、で、これでは終わらない。えっと最後に、もう1曲、みんなに聞いてほしい歌があるにので、
Yes, and it's not over yet. Lastly, there's one more song I want everyone to hear,
その歌を歌ってバイバイしようと思います。では聞いてください。
so I'll sing that and then say goodbye. Please listen.
いかにも弱肉にもお腹Goo Goo
Indeed, even for the weak, my stomach goes Goo Goo
手に持つ砂なめいざZun Zun
Licking the sand in my hand, now Zun Zun
飯は食わねば 寝る寝るNeverな
If I don't eat, I'll sleep, sleep, Never
タイム・スリップ いいーya
Time slip, it's fine
ここどこ迷子でGo Go Go Go
Where am I? A lost child, Go Go Go Go
Dancing ダーウィン じゃんじゃん進化進行
Dancing Darwin, steadily progressing evolution
干渉あり 人類発祥どうこう
Interference exists, something about human origin
ア良い感じ そろそろ出発進行
Ah, feels good, time to depart
去るもの追わ猿ばばびばぶ～
Don't chase those who leave, monkey ba-ba-bi-ba-bu~
(ぷちょへんざっ ぷちょぷちょへんざっ)
(Put your hands up, put-put your hands up)
欲しいモンはほら これだろ旦那
Look, what you want is this, right, sir?
さぁわんわん わんわんわんっ
Now, bow-wow, bow-wow-wow!
チキチキワッハー！
Chiki chiki wa-ha!
脳内全開Yeah やっばっばParty
Brain fully open, Yeah, crazy Party
笑って泣いて踊れば あいあいあっおー
If you laugh, cry, and dance, ai-ai-ah-oh
パンドラ開いて ドヴァッて飲まれたR
Open Pandora, swallowed up by R
ごらん遊ばせ あちゃちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃっパリーン♪
Please have a look, a-cha-cha-i-cha-i-cha-i-shatter♪
おーわっあっ アイアイ 気分はHigh どーんとだ
Oh-wa-ah, ai-ai, mood is High, boom
おーわっあっ アイアイ 愛の間合い どーんとぱ
Oh-wa-ah, ai-ai, distance of love, boom-pah
つながってんだ 記録なんだ Gene & Memeだ 連綿つむいだ 犬猿人神
We're connected, it's a record, Gene & Meme, continuously spun, dog-monkey-human-god
報酬いいんだ 働いてんだ 連動なんだ 休みなし毎日が 月月金土あーん
The reward is good, I'm working, it's linked, every day without rest, Mon-Mon-Fri-Sat-Ahhh
乱心ダーウィン じゃんじゃん淘汰進行
Insane Darwin, steadily progressing selection
人類抹消 あるでしょAI暴走
Human annihilation, AI rampage is possible, right?
アもう最深部 そろそろ計画進行
Ah, already at the deepest part, time to progress the plan
もうゆびゆびまで ワンツースリー おらよーおらよー だんだんすやぁ
Already up to the fingers, one-two-three, here you go, here you go, gradually sleep
オーマイガ　オーマイワイフ
Oh my God, oh my wife
ようやく真理辿り着いた
I've finally reached the truth
無限　螺旋　抜け　無心で
Endless spirals, escaping mindlessly
ほらウェーイ　ほらウェーイ
Look, way! Look, way!
はいっ！
Hai!
（ぷちょへんざっ　ぷちょぷちょへんざっ）
(Put your hands up, put your hands up)
欲しいモンはホラ　これだろ旦那
Look, the thing you want is this, right hubby?
さぁわんわん　わんわんわんっ　ワンッ
Now, woof woof, woof woof woof, woof!
チキチキワッハー！
Chiki chiki wa-ha!
脳内全開Yeah　やっぱっぱParty
Brain wide open Yeah, yappa-ppa party
笑って泣いて踊れば　あいあいあーおー
If you laugh, cry, and dance, ai-ai-ah-oh
パンドラ開けて　ドヴァッて飲まれたRaw
Open Pandora, swallowed up in a rush, Raw
ごらん遊ばせ　あちゃちゃいちゃといちゃいちゃっぱ
Please take a look, acha-chai-chato-icha-icha-ppa
おーわっあっ　アイアイ　気分はHigh　とんとんたん
Oh-wa-at, ai-ai, feeling high, ton-ton-tan
おーわっあっ　アイアイ　愛の間合い　どんどんぱん
Oh-wa-at, ai-ai, the distance of love, don-don-pan
ぷちょへんざっ
Put your hands up
はい！
Yes!
今のは、えーオリジナル曲なんですけど、
That was, uh, an original song,
えーこのあとですねすぐにMVも公開するので、
and, uh, the MV will be released right after this,
ぜひぜひそちらもリスナーさんみんなに楽しんでほしいなと思います。
so I definitely want all my listeners to enjoy that too.
めっちゃね、可愛くてかっこよく仕上がってるからね、ぜひみんな見てください。
It turned out really cute and cool, so please check it out, everyone.
で、
And,
みんなにころねは、今日は渡すものがありまーす。
Korone has something to give to everyone today.
いつもはね、帰ってこないあれを今日はね返すんだよ。
I'm going to return that thing that usually never comes back today.
ちょっと待っててね。
Wait just a moment.
はぁ、あー新鮮だ。新鮮な...
Hah, ah, it's fresh. Fresh...
...指だよ。ほらさっき取っちゃってごめんね。
...fingers. Here, sorry I took them earlier.
はい、みんなどうぞ。
Here, everyone, go ahead.
なんでいらないの？
Why don't you want them?
なんで？
Why?
みんなのでしょ？はい。
They're yours, right? Here.
えー、なんで？はい。
Eh, why? Here.
え、なんで？なんで？ほらほら、素敵。
Eh, why? Why? Look, look, they're lovely.
おいしそ...おいしそうじゃない。はい、はい。
They look deli... not delicious. Here, here.
はい、返すよ。はい、はい、はい。
Here, I'm returning them. Here, here, here.
はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい。
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
はい、おら！おらおら！
Here, take 'em! Take 'em, take 'em!
はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい、はい。
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.